♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?
♪ Lucky there's a family guy
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us
♪ Laugh and cry
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪ Family Guy 11x19 ♪Save the Clam
拯救醉蛤
翻译：螃蟹阿雪 注释:螃蟹阿雪 校对： 压制: @familyguy贴吧字幕组
好了 醉蛤队 此刻
All right, Drunken Clammers, this is it,
本赛季最重要的比赛
the most important game of the season.
现在 大家都醉了吧
Now, is everybody drunk?
当然 好 不错
Completely.Okay, good.
还有是不是没人做热身
And did nobody warm up?
不错 因为没什么比僵硬的中年身体
Good. 'Cause there's nothing an unstretched middle-aged body
更加像是参加剧烈运动了（？）
likes more than explosive movements.
记住 我们来这是要以自己都不熟悉的一面
Now remember, we're here to impress the girlfriends
震惊那些女朋友的
of guys we barely know,
所以投球时 要像加农炮一样
so when you get the ball, throw it like a cannon.
每次一定要把你们的手臂甩出去
You must throw your arm out on every play.
还有别的关于垒球的问题吗
Any other softball-related questions?
我有问题
Yeah, I got a question:
能不能在结束后把我们不环保的
Can we leave our bad-for-the-environment
塑料泡沫冷藏箱丢下?
Styrofoam coolers behind when we leave?
可以 你必须把它们扔下
Yes, you must leave them behind,
而且必须是一堆残渣的形式
and they must be in a crumbly mess
那么城市清洁工就必须在起风时
so that the city clean-up workers have to chase
去追那些小泡沫
the little bits when the wind blows.
其实 Stewie 这是一个很不错的公园
You know, Stewie, this is actually a good park.
我已经在这找到了很多老网球
I've found a lot of old tennis balls here.
呃 我不关心这个地方
Eh, I don't care for this place.
上一次我来这儿
Last time I was here,
我不小心走进了一个西班牙野餐趴
I accidentally walked into a Spanish picnic.
抱歉 这里有人见一个玩具车了吗
Excuse me, has anyone seen a toy car around here?
哦 婴儿
Ooh. Es baby.
我 做的 美丽
I make beautiful.
别对Julio动歪脑筋
Don't get any ideas about Julio.
我才是他首选
I'm his number one.
Goldman药店队来了
Here comes Goldman's Pharmacy.
嘿 Goldman药店队
Hey, Goldman's Pharmacy!
能给我们填一个腹泻的诊断表吗
Can you fill out a prescription for us for diarrhea?
我们准备好排泄(跑垒)了
We're about to get the runs!
哦 是吗? 说起
Oh, yeah? Well, speaking of things
棕色又可以跑(排泄)的东西
that are brown and can run,
见见我们的新队友
meet our new teammate!
我勒个去 他们找了个替身
Holy crap.They got a ringer.
搞毛啊? Jerome 在你们队?
What the hell? Jerome's on your team?
Jerome曾代替Cleveland的黑人 见S08E07
没错 我们是在他在我药店
That's right.We got to know each other
附近晃悠时认识的
while I was following him around my store.
咋啦 傻货们 我想
What's up, fools?I'd like to dedicate
以我今天的表现献给惠特妮休斯顿小姐
my performance today to Miss Whitney Houston.
噢 我们要被**了
Oh, we are (bleep).
上啊 Jerome
Come on, Jerome!
打出全垒打我就能
Get a hit so I can bring
为我父母带个体育运动奖杯回去
a sports trophy home for my parents!
Jeffrey Lipsitz有两个足球奖章!
Jeffrey Lipsitz has two soccer medals!
我不能踢足球 我的踝是婴儿状腿
I can't play soccer--I have newborn-calf ankles!
你知道的 该死!
You know this, damn it!
我要给这个新球开球了
I'm gonna tear the cover off this ball.
不过 等一下 要先调整一下自己的状态
But, hang on, first I got to adjust myself.
你在过一个美好的早晨吗?
Are you having a nice morning, dear?
哦没错 我喜欢住在这里 （?）
Oh, yes, I love living here,in the next town over.
小妞击球!
All right, chick batter!
所有人前移
Everyone bring it in!
往前移
Bring it on in!
一击必中 宝贝
Get a hit, babe!
你知道的 宝贝
You know it, babe.
好吧 退回去!退回去!
All right, move it back!Move it back!
Peter 为什么你看起来如此紧张
Peter, why do you look so nervous?
我给一住院的孩子许诺必为他打一个本垒打
I promised a kid in the hospital I'd hit a home run for him.
抱歉 我三振出局了
Sorry, I struck out looking.
等等 你不是那个我许诺的孩子
Wait, you're not the kid I promised.
不是 他昨晚死了
No, he died last night.
哦 呼唷
Oh, phew.
伙计们 再打出一个我们就赢了
All right, guys, one more out and the game is ours.
加油 Horace 振他出局
Come on, Horace!Strike him out!
Horace!你还好吗?
Horace! You okay?
哦天 他伤的不轻
Oh, my God!He's really hurt bad!
顺便说下 你出垒线了
You're out of the baseline,by the way.
你出局了 比赛结束
You're out. Game's over.
哦 天啊 Horace伤得很重
But, oh, my God,Horace is really hurt.
他死了
He's dead.
愿他安息
Let him rest in peace.
让我们给他盖些树叶
Let's put some leaves on him
然后买雪糕吃
and go get some ice cream.
圆蛤殡仪馆
我无法相信Horace死了
I can't believe Horace is dead.
我无法相信我们把Brian留在封闭的车里了
I can't believe we left Brian in the car with the windows up.
我要尿尿
I'm gonna pee!
听着 对此我感到很难受
Listen, I just feel awful about this.
Horace是个好酒吧招待 也是个好人
Horace was a good bartender and a good guy.
我真希望这儿有什么我能做的
I wish there was something I could do.
我们知道你不是真心的 Jerome
Well, we know you didn't mean it, Jerome.
那是个很糟糕的状况
It's just a terrible situation.
就像你是唯一一个在餐桌上
Like when you're the only one at the table
点单不被服务生赞赏的人
where the waiter doesn't say, "Good order."
我要比目鱼 啊好选择
I'll have the halibut.Ah, great choice.
大厨特选之一 你会爱上它的
One of the chef's specialties; you'll love it.
鲜鱼捕于10里以内的水域
It was caught fresh less than ten miles from here.
我要纽约风味牛前腰牛排
I'll have the New York strip steak.
嗯 绝对是这里我的最爱
Mmm! My absolute favorite dish here.
完美的刀工 绝佳的调味
It is a spectacular cut,superbly seasoned
以及那大理石肉纹是我见过最好的
and the marbling is some of the best I've ever seen.
还有我点鸡肉
And I'll have the chicken.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我只是想说...
I'd just like to say that...
今天之前 我不知道明斯特一家是
before today, I didn't know the Munsters were driving around
Munsters 70年代讲述善良的怪物一家的情景喜剧
开殡葬车周游的
in a funeral car.
我开始觉得那个电视的所有东西
I'm beginning to think everything on that show
就是个大玩笑
was a big joke.
我 呃 我就是想
I'd, um... I'd just like...
当 当你失去
Whe... When you lose...
还有很 还有很多
Um, there's so... There's so mu...
还有很多
There's so much...
我  我
I... I...
谢谢你 Quagmire
Thank you, Quagmire.
也许还是有些"男人"愿意说几句话
Perhaps there are some men who would like to say a few words.
Horace掌管醉蛤30多年
Horace owned the Clam for over 30 years.
这段时间 他深入我们所有人的生命
During that time,he touched all of our lives.
他是一个伟大的酒吧招待以及伟大的朋友
He was a great bartender and a great friend.
那么让我们回顾他的人生
And so let us take a look back on his life
通过这个记录了
through this video commemorating all the DUI's
所有与他有关酒驾的视频
that he was responsible for.
我会记得你
♪ I will remember you
此处为Sarah Mclachlan的"I Will Remember You"
你是否会记得我
♪ Will you remember me?
别让你的人生
♪ Don't let your life
匆匆流逝
♪ Pass you by
ET外星人:嗷
E.T.:Ouch.
这里有厕所吗
Is there a bathroom in here?
我憋这泡大便已经20分钟了
I've been yo-yoing a turd for the last 20 minutes.
哦 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我在找厕所
I was looking for the bathroom.
是我不该没锁门
I shouldn't have left the door open.
抱歉你可能会被恶心到
Sorry if you're grossed out by this.
没 没 没 我只是
No. No, no, I'm just...
不常见不在厕所的大个尸体(弃婴么)
not used to seeing corpses that big and not in a toilet.
哦 我来帮你吧
Oh, here, let me help you with that.
好了
There you go.
你已经准备好参加你的大日子了
Now you're all set for your big day.
谢谢 我可以雇佣些兼职在这里
Thanks. You know, I could use some part-time help here
帮忙处理尸体 如果你有兴趣的话
preparing the bodies,if you're interested.
真的吗 耶 那 那真是太好了
Really? Yeah,that'd-that'd be great.
有钱赚了
I could use the money,
而且我有点不想去我上一个工作了
and I'm getting kind of tired of my old job.
领先的两名选手只有0.5分之差
Only a half a point divides our top two competitors
现在进入最后一个项目 Meg卷
as we enter the last event,the Meg Roll.
你觉得Horace葬礼之后我们就是买醉
You think it's cool to go drinking
合适吗?
right after Horace's funeral?
当然 那是他愿意看到的
Of course. It's what he would've wanted.
听着 我们都要跨过这槛
Listen, we all got to move on.
正如特工处在1963年11月23那天一样
Like the Secret Service did on November 23, 1963.
特工处负责美国总统副总统的安全护卫工作 63年11月22日肯尼迪遇刺
好吧 伙计们 我知道昨天
All right, guys,I know that yesterday
总统遇刺后计时
对于我们是艰难的一天
was a rough one for us.
不过很骄傲的宣布
But it's with great pride
我要把这个0翻成1了
that I'm gonna turn this zero into a one.
好哎
All right!
尼克 你应该回家换身衣服
Nichols, you should go home and change.
搞毛啊?嘿伙计 你在做什么?
What the hell?Hey, pal, what're you doing?
这是我们的酒吧
This is our bar.
不再是了
Not anymore.
Horace欠了比这地方价值还多的债
Horace owed more than this place is worth,
所以现在它是银行的了
so it's the bank's now.
我很抱歉 但是醉蛤永久性关闭了
I'm sorry but The Drunken Clam is permanently closed.
关闭?!
Closed?!
这是黑暗时代的开始
That was the start of the dark times.
银行夺走了我们的酒吧 我们的营生 然后是我们的家
The banks took our bars, our businesses and then our homes.
必须要做出改变
A change had to be made.
一个只有一个人可以做的改变
A change only one man could make.
我是制风者
I am the Wind Maker...
我现在射杀猴子
...and I shoot monkeys now.
我们现在回到Joanie爱Chris Brown
We now return to Joanie Loves Chris Brown.
Joanie! Chris!
欢迎来参加派对 我能给你几拳吗?
Welcome to the party.Can I offer you some punch?
不 谢谢了 我在车里来过了
No, thanks. I had some in the car.
Joanie爱Chris Brown是在感觉并
Joanie Loves Chris Brown was taped in front
不舒适的观众前录制的
of a very uncomfortable studio audience.
天 关掉醉蛤真让人不爽
Man, it really sucks they closed down the Clam.
没错 不过 我 我是说 这也不错 对吧?
Yeah, but I... I mean,this is good, right?
我是说 至少有地方让我们喝酒以及让
I mean, as long as we got a place to drink and a restroom
商业人士同性性交的休息室
for businessmen to have homosexual encounters.
嘿 谢谢刚才那一炮
Hey, thanks for the sex.
谢谢你公证那些文件
Thank you for notarizing those documents.
Peter 下面这是怎么了?
Peter, what's going on down here?
为什么地板上都是啤酒瓶
Why are there beer bottles all over the floor?
我们需要个新地方喝酒 Lois
Well, we needed a new spot to drink, Lois.
省省吧 Peter
Forget it, Peter.
你不能把我们的客厅变成酒吧
You're not turning our living room into a bar.
别这样 Lois 人家需要个地方喝酒
Oh, come on, Lois, we got to have a place to drink.
喝酒是唯一可以让
Drinking is the only thing
友情维持的事情
holding this friendship together.
每次我们试着做严肃的事都以失败告终
Everything we try to do sober just ends badly.
我不认为剧本以此开头较好
I just don't think a good way to start a screenplay is,
"400年前Maryland的Bethesda"
"400 years ago in Bethesda, Maryland."
没错 而且不觉得每一个角色
Yeah, and don't you think it's confusing that every character
都叫电影角色很让人迷惑么 快点 你们
in the movie is named Movie Guy? Come on, you guys.
奥斯卡就在下周 我们把这个搞完
The Oscars are next week,so let's get this done.
Meg 楼上需要我 所以你要完成这个
Meg, I'm needed upstairs,so I'll let you finish up.
这儿和那儿铺点粉就好
Just put some blush here and here.
这样让眼睛看起来不那么死沉空洞
It makes the eyes look a little less dead and hollow.
哇哦 真的有作用
Wow, that really works.
嗯 也许我自己也应该试试
Hmm. Maybe I'll try that on myself.
哦呃 你是那种我们叫做"盖棺脸"型
Oh, uh... you have what we call a "closed casket face."
嘿 Meg 你和谁约会呢?
Hey, Meg,who's your date?
他看起来像真正的死尸
He looks like a real stiff.
Chris 你来这儿搞毛啊?
Chris, what the hell are you doing here?
我告诉过你工作时候别来烦我
I told you not to bother me at work.
我被锁外面了 需要你的钥匙
I got locked out of the house,and I need your key.
不是吧!你要和这些死尸打交道?
No way! You get to work with all these dead people?
嘿 看 这哥们在挖鼻孔
Hey, look,this guy's picking his nose.
看 现在他在吃鼻屎
Look, now he's eating it!
Chris 停手!
Chris! Knock it off!
你会让我惹上麻烦的
You're gonna get me in trouble!
Meg 他们都死了
Meg, they're dead.
你能不能别这么紧张
Would you stop being so uptight?
你就像那种参加过越战的
You're like one of those Asian-Americans
亚裔美国人
who fought in Vietnam.
哦 这是我
Oh, it's just me.
Peter 我以为你要带我们去新的喝酒地儿
Peter, I thought you were taking us to a new drinking spot.
我们来醉蛤做什么 听着
What are we doing at the Clam?Look, guys,
我们试过别的酒吧 我们试过在家喝酒
we tried other bars,we tried drinking at home,
我们甚至试了会改变一切的
we even tried the big end-of-the-year
高中毕业大趴体
high school party that will change everything.
如果我们今晚不解决处男身份
If we don't lose our virginity tonight,
那大学也解决不好了
we're never gonna make it in college!
嘿 Peter哪了
Hey, where's Peter?
只是在和咱校最火辣的阿曼达交谈
Only talking to Amanda Small,the hottest girl in school.
不过你不是和Joanne Fuller一起吗?
But aren't you going out with Joanne Fuller?
JoJo?不 她是我邻居 我一直认识她(?)
JoJo? No, she's my neighbor.I've known her forever.
她在她爸爸的车库工作
She works at her dad's garage.
某种意义说她就是个爷们
She's practically a guy.
JoJo?!
♪透过窗口...♪
♪ Looking from a window above... ♪
此处为Yazoo的"Only You"
嗨 Peter
Hi, Peter.
我以为你在刻车库雕刻?
But I thought you was workin'on your garbage sculpture.
我必须先见个人
There was someone I had to see first.
抱歉 阿曼达 根据80年代电影定律
Sorry, Amanda.By the law of '80s movies,
一个新晋变身的假小子
a newly transformed tomboy
超越了你的持久的热辣
supersedes your long-standing hotness.
♪我所知的一切
♪ And all I ever knew
♪只有你
♪ Only you...
♪
承认吧 只有一个为我们准备的喝酒地儿
Let's face it-- there's only one drinking spot for us,
就是醉蛤 但是Peter 它关门了
and it's the Clam.But, Peter, it's closed.
我们不能进去
We can't go in there.
Quagmire当一个女孩说她不想
Quagmire, when a girl says she doesn't want
和你打炮 你会接受这个回答吗?
to have sex with you,do you take that as an answer?
我的律师建议我不回答这个问题
My lawyer has advised me not to answer that question.
我打赌你能挤进那个窗户
Look, I bet you could squeeze through that window.
这儿就没关
It's not even locked.
而且酒还都在那儿
And all the booze is still in there.
别介 这是非法入侵
Come on, guys,this is trespassing
违法的
and it's against the law.
也许我们应该让醉蛤就这么算了
Maybe we should just let the Clam go
以及 比如 多花点时间
and, I don't know,spend more time
和家人相处
with our families.
嗯 我试过这个
Yeah, I tried that.
我就是多花了点时间
I just spend most of the time
检查Chris是不是自闭症
testing Chris to see if he's autistic.
不!
No!
未过度表达
Not overly affectionate.
兄弟们 这才是我们的归属之地
Guys, this is where we belong.
的确 没人质疑这个
Yeah, no question about that.
我们在这里生根
Yeah, we got roots here.
我们这15年一直在这儿
We've been coming to this place for 15 years.
我们的根比这个还遥远
Our roots go back further than that.
我祖父曾在我还小时
My grandfather used to bring me here
带我来这儿
when I was a kid.
他的祖父带他来这儿
And his grandfather brought him here.
日安 先生
Good day, gentlemen!
欢迎来到醉蛤酒吧
Welcome to the Drunken Clam!
能为你们提供杯黑啤吗?
Can I get you boys a mug of stout?
当然
Why, certainly.
这是个一流的酒吧 你来过了
This is a bully establishment you've got here.
门有点矮
The doors are a little short,
不过还行
but that's okay,
因为回到这年代我们都要矮一点
because we're smaller back now.
敬醉蛤
To the Clam!
敬
Hear, hear!
敬脑损伤性病
And to brain-damaging venereal disease.
我醒来时候阴茎枕头上有血
I wake up with blood on my penis pillow.
我要开始在轮椅上
I'm gonna go insane
发疯 从海洋开始
in a wheelchair,staring at the sea.
这是一切关于...
This is everything about..
如果这是醉蛤 我爱它
if it's the Clam, I love it.
我要去 当然了
I was just gonna... that's exactly.
嘿 呃 记得 记得 记得 那时...
Hey, uh, remember...remember-remember when...
记得那时 记得那时Quicktime
remember when... remember when Quicktime here
经过这个包厢 在这个包厢
passed out in this...in this booth...
这个包厢 我们对他做了
this booth,and we did stuff to him
你对小妞们做的事 并且我们 我们许诺
that you do to ladies and we-we promised
我们永远不告诉你
we'd never tell you.
啥...？
Wha...?
敬醉蛤
To the Clam!
Joe 你 你的头发看起来很蠢
Joe, you-- wha...your hair looks stupid.
所有 所有最伟大的
All... all the greatest...
所有我生命中最伟大的时刻
all the greatest moments of my life,
我都在这个 这个包厢渡过的
I spent right here in-in this booth.
Maggie第一次讲话
Maggie's first word.
开始回忆辛普森一家的Peter
Bart飞跃峡谷
Bart jumping that canyon.
Plow先生
Mr. Plow.
所有我生命最伟大的时刻
All the greatest moments of my life.
为什么 为什么商标人
Why is... why is Label Guy
要打我?
trying to punch me?
先打到你了 商标人
Punch you first, Label Guy.
我要去小便
I got to go pee.
我不想起来
I don't want to get up.
Joe 那 那个东西哪儿了?
Joe, where's the... that thing?
那东西哪儿了?导尿管哪儿了?
Where's the thing?Where's the catheter thing?
不行 是我的 是专属的
No, it's mine,it's private.
嘿 如果我吹这一端会发生什么
Hey, what happens if I blow in this end?
别 我会爆炸的
Don't, I'll 'splode.
我要
I'm gonna.
你比Bonnie做的好
You do it better than Bonnie.
男人知道男人喜欢什么
It takes a man to know what a man likes.
Meg Dougan家打电话他们现在想
Meg, the Dougan family called and they now want
Dougan先生明天的守灵穿灰色西装
Mr. Dougan in a gray suit for the wake tomorrow.
因为这很重要
'Cause it so matters.
你能帮忙换他的衣服吗?
Could you change his suit, please?
可以 我一会儿回来
Sure.I'll be back in a bit.
我滴神啊
Oh... my... God!
好吧Chris 它在哪儿?
All right, Chris,where is it?
另外别装着像是
And don't try to act like
你不知道我在说什么
you don't know what I'm talking about.
好吧 被你发现了
Fine, you caught me.
我偷穿你的胸罩
So I borrowed your bra.
人家下楼的时候乳头疼
My boobs hurt when I go down the stairs!
不 不是这个 傻货
No, not that, you idiot.
死尸哪里去了
Where is the dead body?
我知道你拿了
I know you took it.
别撒谎 否则我就告诉Jennifer Connelly
And don't lie, or I'll tell Jennifer Connelly
Jennifer Connelly 美国女性 主演过美丽心灵
你就是那个一直寄
that you're the one who's been mailing her
狗头给她的人
those dog heads.
呃 是的 我想寄这个给一个婊子
Uh, yes, I'd like to mail this to a whore.
好吧 好了 Meg
Okay, fine, Meg!
我用尸体潜入了R级电影
I used the body to get me into R-rated movies.
之后我带他去游泳
After that,I took him swimming
然后他就分尸了
and he fell apart.
Chris Dougan先生明天出殡
Chris, Mr. Dougan's wake is tomorrow,
那棺材必须有一个尸体
and there's going to be a body in that casket.
如果不是他的 那就是你的
If it's not his,it's going to be yours.
嘿 伙计们 怎么样
Hey, guys,what's goin' on?
没人说一句话
And no one says anything,
就说明他们讨厌这件衣服
which means they hate it.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
我醉得太厉害了
I am so hung over.
我也是
Me, too.
幸运的是 我醉的时候
But luckily,when I'm hung over,
我可以直接蜕皮成另一个Peter
I can just molt into another Peter.
哇哦 好棒
Wow, that's amazing.
没错 但是接下来的十分钟
Yeah, but for the next ten minutes,
我会变得脆弱易被捕食者攻击
I'll be very vulnerable to predators.
山狮子
Mountain lion.
让你自己看起来很大
Make yourself look big!
搞毛啊
What the hell?
外面有几辆推土机
There's a bunch of bulldozers out there.
停下 停下 这 这里怎么了?
Hold it, hold it!What-what's going on?
我们是来拆这个的
We're here to demolish this building
受命于银行
by order of the bank.
TMD知道是
Like hell you are!
你 你在说什么 Peter
Wh-What are you talking about, Peter?
我们哪儿也不去
We ain't goin' nowhere.
这个酒吧属于我们
This bar belongs to us.
冰激凌车
Ice cream truck!
你没买到冰激凌?
You didn't get any ice cream?
卖冰激凌的男人很帅
The ice cream man was handsome.
人家紧张
I got nervous.
我们中断此节目
We interrupt this program
带来一个五频道重大消息
for a Channel Five breaking news report.
三个当地人阻拦在
Three local men have barricaded themselves
一个圆蛤酒吧 并且当前
inside a Quahog bar,and are currently
与当局僵持不下
in a standoff with authorities.
我们转给Joyce Kinney直播
We now go live to Joyce Kinney,
她昨晚参加了她妹妹的婚礼
who attended her sister's wedding last night.
谢谢Tom
Thanks, Tom.
嫌疑人之一
One of the suspects has been
被指认为Peter Griffin
identified as Peter Griffin.
不过真实故事是
But the real story is,
我也能成为已婚
I'd be married, too,
如果我愿意和波斯人约会
if I were willing to date a Persian.
他们发现他了
Guys, they found him.
不用管宣传单了
Don't bother with the posters.
天啊 Peter咋想的
My God,what is Peter thinking?!
失踪:迟缓的中年男人
是啊 他就像一个连环杀手一样疯狂
Yes, he's crazy as a serial killer.
好了 你最后一餐想吃什么?
All right, what do you want for your last meal?
呃 我想我就来份沙拉好了
Uh, I think I'll just have a salad.
边上放点调味料
Dressing on the side.
我昨天午餐吃的巨多
I had a huge last lunch.
里面的人听着
All right, listen up in there!
不要让这原本容易的事变得艰难
Let's not make this any harder than it has to be.
我们这有很多傻警察
We have a lot of dumb cops here.
这太疯狂了
Guys, this is crazy.
此外 我是个警察
Plus, I'm a cop.
我不能参与这个
I can't be a part of this.
别这样 Joe这是我们的酒吧
Come on, Joe, this is our bar.
这是我们三个撰写自杀公约
It's where the three of us made that suicide pact
Quagmire和我会在最后几分钟出去(?)
that Quagmire and I are gonna back out of at the last minute.
我很抱歉 但是那是我的工作
I'm sorry, guys,but it's my job.
我要养一家人
I got a family to support.
混蛋
That jerk!
他怎么能配上我们?
How could he desert us?
放松Quagmire 他只是做他的本职工作
Relax, Quagmire,he's just doing his job.
你会原谅他的
You'll forgive him.
就像Kathleen Turner原谅了她的镜子
Just like Kathleen Turner forgave her mirror.
Kathleen Turner(1954-)美国影星
抱歉
Sorry.
证明你对我说的是对的
Turns out you were right about me.
长官 等下
Officer, wait!
我是他妻子 给我那个喇叭
I'm his wife;give me that bullhorn.
Peter 你马上从这里出去
Peter, you get out here right now,
否则我就扔了
or else I'm throwing away
所有你的土豆脑袋先生 我发誓
all of your Mr. Potato Heads, I swear.
没关系 她只知道诱饵在哪儿
It's okay, she only knows where the decoys are.
Swanson 你在这儿
Swanson, there you are.
听着 你处理这个麻烦
Listen, you hang out at this dump.
我想要你进去解决这事儿
I want you to go in there and end this thing.
我会尽最大努力 长官
I'll do my best, sir.
这是我们的酒吧
This is our bar.
这是我们友谊的基石
It's the cornerstone of our friendship.
Joe 这是Tim Gunn
Joe, this is Tim Gunn.
Tim Gunn美国时尚顾问
我认可你朋友说的
I agree with your friend.
我要让那个人从我脑袋里出去
I got to get that guy out of my head.
看 他们派Joe进来了
Look, they're sending Joe in.
好 听着 伙计们
All right, listen up, fellas.
Joe 等下 放下你的枪
Joe, wait, put your gun down.
在这冲突没有意义
There's no point in fighting anymore.
我们会安静地离开
We'll leave quietly.
当然你们会
Like hell you will.
这是我们的醉蛤
This is our Clam,
我们不会让他们接手这儿的
and we are not gonna let them take it.
耶 好哎 好哎 耶
Yay! All right!All right! Yeah!
我们爱Joe
We love Joe!
Swanson 这儿他妈是怎么回事?
Swanson, what the hell's going on in here?
抱歉 长官
I'm sorry, Chief.
我实在无法让他们拆了这儿
I just can't let them bulldoze this building.
嘿 Joe 这是那个老婆是
Hey, Joe, is this the same chief
真狗的那个长官吗?
whose wife is a real hog?
Swanson 别学傻瓜
Swanson, don't be a fool.
你真想在这里了结你的职业生涯吗
You really want to throw away your career on this?
你们的酒吧已经没了
Guys, your bar is gone.
既然是银行的财产
And since it's bank property,
除了逮捕你们我别无选择
I have no choice but to place you all under arrest.
它不再是银行的财产了
It ain't bank property no more.
Jerome?!你来这儿做什么
Jerome?!What are you doing here?
听着 这所有的事情发生
Listen, it's kind of all my fault
算是我的错
this happened in the first place.
我造成了Horace的死亡
I'm responsible for Horace's death.
此外 作为一个前运动员 我有义务
Plus, as a former athlete,it's my responsibility
投资我的收入到饭店 酒吧
to invest my earnings in a restaurant, bar,
或者汽车代理
or car dealership.
你玩什么运动
What sport did you play?
长曲棍球
Lacrosse.
也是我哥哥的名字(兄弟乱伦么)
Which is also my brother's name.
对于我对Horace做的事情很抱歉
Look, I felt bad about what I did to Horace.
所以 当我听到
So, when I heard on the news
他们要拆他的酒吧
that they were tearing down his bar,
我把买下酒吧当做继承Horace遗产
I saw buying it as a way to carry on Horace's legacy.
所以现在是我拥有醉蛤了
So I own the Clam now.
长官你可以解除警卫了
Chief, you can call off your cops.
你可以放那些推土机回家了
And you can send those bulldozers home.
耶 醉蛤得救了
Yay, the Clam is saved!
耶 好哎
Yeah! All right.
我们做到了
We pulled it off, guys.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
全都是因为我相信自己
And all because I believed in myself
正如Pop-Pop说的一样
like Pop-Pop always said.
请给我毒鼠强
Please give me rat poison,
我就只想死
I want only to die.
不行 我们试过了 Pop-Pop
No, we did it, Pop-Pop.
Meg 这家人都来了
Meg, the family is here
为Dougan守灵
for Mr. Dougan's wake,
那么你可以带尸体来了吗
so could you please bring in the body?
Meg 我不要做这个
Meg, I'm not doing this.
你别无选择 Chris
You have to, Chris.
姐弟之间要互相照应
Siblings have to look out for each other.
正如Manning家
Like the Mannings.
Eli你扔了三次触地得分
Eli, you threw for three touchdowns today,
其实不错 除了Peyton扔了四次
which isn't bad,except Peyton had four.
嗯 Cooper申请Visa卡得到初步许可了
Well, Cooper got pre-approved for a Visa card today.
别这样 我们今天都渡过了不错的一天
Come on, guys,we all had a good day.
停下
Stop it.
我痒痒
I have an itch.
我不在乎
I don't care.
死人不会挠他们的球儿
Dead people don't scratch their balls.
我控制不了
Well, I can't help it.
是这该死的羊毛裤子
It's these damn wool pants.
我要出"香蕉"了(？)
I'm going bananas.
如果我不能挠 你必须替我挠
If I can't scratch them,you have to.
就是 呃 把他的裤子拽平一点
Just, uh, straightening out his pants a little.
哦 是的 是的 这不错
Oh, yeah...yeah, that's good.
挠它 挠它
Scratch it. Scratch it.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
嗨 我是Hellen Dougan
Hello, I'm Helen Dougan.
我丈夫在死之前签了
My husband had filled out an organ donor card
器官捐赠卡
before he passed away,
一个女士刚在一次事故中失去了她的脸
and a woman just lost her face in a freak accident.
黑猩猩袭击受害人得到新脸
Chimp attack victim gets new face
史上第一个成功脸移植者也是被黑猩猩袭击
Meg 虽然你无法辨识 我在皱眉
Meg, though you cannot tell,I am frowning.
盛大重新开业
哇哦 Jerome 这地方看起来棒极了
Wow, Jerome, the place looks great.
耶 看看你 拥有一个酒吧
Yeah, look at you,owning a bar.
你们做得不错
You guys are doing pretty good.
之前经营索马里 现在这个
First you get to run Somalia, now this.
能重回醉蛤
Well, it sure is good
的确是很好
to be back in the old Clam.
嘿 有几个人坐在我们的包厢
Hey, there's some guys sitting in our booth.
也许我们应该告诉他们那时我们的包厢
Maybe we should tell them it's our booth.
呃呃 或者我们可以就坐在地板上
Uh-huh. Or we could just sit on the floor,
靠在这些垃圾筒边上
next to these garbage cans.
白人啊!
恐惧每个种族!